好了 大家聚过来
Okay, everybody, gather 'round.
谁能想到今天是"带女朋友上班"日?
Who knew it was "bring your girlfriend to work" day?
她不是我女朋友
She is not my girlfriend.
Judy是心肺复苏娃娃
Judy is a CPR doll,
也是这家餐厅里最努力干活的姑娘
and the hardest-working girl in this diner.
哦 Han 你不该把你的性玩偶带到公共场合
Oh, Han, you shouldn't bring your sex doll out in public.
这不是我女朋友 也不是性玩偶!
This is not my girlfriend or a sex doll!
Earl 过来
Earl, come over.
我们要用Judy来学习复苏方法
We're going to use Judy to learn how to resuscitate.
我有"不要复苏"的条款
I have a "do not resuscitate" clause,
同样的 我也不会复苏别人
as in, I do not resuscitate others.
Oleg 过来
Oleg.
怎么了 Han?
What's up, Han?
哦 嘿 Judy
Oh, hey, Judy.
你怎么认识Judy?
How do you know Judy?
有这待身躯的美娇娘 能横行天下
With a torso like that, she gets around.
好了 我来演示一下
Okay, I will demonstrate.
哦 不!
Oh, no!
Judy被东西呛到了!
Judy's choking on something!
我们知道这不是你
Well, we know it's not you.
首先 你要把头后仰
First you have to tilt the head back
让呼吸畅通 然后吹气
and clear the airway and blow.
哦 Max 我想我们正在见证
Oh, Max, I think we're witnessing
他的初吻
his first kiss.
第四次 谢谢
Fourth, thank you very much.
Han 你干嘛浪费时间亲她?
Han, why are you wasting your time kissing her?
她都没有手
She doesn't have any arms.
直接做吧
Just go for it.
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组  http://hdscg.com/ ==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 。沫
时间轴: 。沫
翻译: Astral  波特妹子  落寞卷菜
校对: 桃茜茜
大家好吗? 今天是个重大日子
What's up, everybody? Big day today.
虽然没圣诞节那么重大 但这标志着
Not as big as Christmas, but still marks the arrival
有人的幸福时刻即将来临 就是我
of someone very blessed: me.
好 我们懂了
Yeah, we get it.
你说起自己的生日
You talk about your birthday
比坎耶・维斯特(歌手)说唱自己的名字还多
more than Kanye West talks about Kanye West.
Caroline 我还以为你会哭呢
Caroline, I thought you would be crying.
能预料到你会在生日时泪崩
Tears on your birthday have become as expected
就如能料到前迪士尼明星会去戒毒所一样
as an ex-Disney star going to rehab.
我为什么要伤心?
Why would I be sad?
我拥有健康 和正在萌芽的生意...
I have my health, a business that's budding...
但却没有胸
Boobs that aren't.
我不过生日
I don't believe in birthdays.
只有心态才能决定你的年龄
You're only as old as you feel.
这会让我永远年轻
Which makes me nothing years old.
说到"年轻"...
Speaking of nothing...
Caroline 我们今晚照旧去"双靴"披萨店吗?
Caroline, are we still on for Two Boots pizza tonight?
为了庆祝你的生日 我会早点关门
I'm closing the diner early in honor of your birthday,
绝不是因为
and just not because the city
市里要求检查黑曲霉的情况
has demanded to look into the black mold situation.
当然了 Han
Absolutely, Han.
你可以点一份披萨加两种配汁
You can have one slice with two toppings
也可以点两份披萨加一种配汁
or two slices with one topping,
还有 我的生日蛋糕是免费的果馅饼
and my birthday cake is a free flan
因为我跟洗碗工调情了
'cause I flirted with the dishwasher.
Caroline 亲爱的 我要是你
Caroline, sweetheart, if I was you,
我会直接撞穿厚玻璃板的窗户
I would just put my head through a plate glass window.
好了 各位
Okay, everybody.
我有两个通知 都是好消息
I have two announcements, both good news.
第一 那个在三明治里发现鸟喙的人
First, the guy who found the beak in his sandwich
决定不起诉了 第二
is not suing, and second,
我打算向Sopie表露个问题
I'm gonna pop the question to Sophie.
反正你已经把什么都给露了
Well, you've already popped everything else.
你们怎么看?
What do you think?
他们说钻石是女孩子最好的朋友
They say diamonds are a girl's best friend.
哦 真的吗?
Oh, really?
我以为女孩子最好的朋友是
I thought a girl's best friend
某个只比她胖一点的人
was someone just a little fatter than her.
这是我远在俄国的奶奶的
It was my grandma's from Russia.
我让我表妹Svela吞了它
I had my cousin Svela swallow it
以便带来美国
to bring it to America.
她过了海关以后 把这个拉出来的
She passed customs, then she passed this.
喝了五六瓶漱口水后 嘭!
Five, six rinses later, boom!
免税
Duty free.
好吧 看来这个比在婚戒店买的要好
Well, I guess that's better than getting it at Kay.
Sophie想要这个吗?
Is Sophie expecting it?
当然
Of course.
她不喜欢惊喜
She doesn't like surprises
因为她家谷仓曾被
since her family barn was torched
一个精神不稳定的雇农给烧了
by a mentally unstable farmhand.
你好 这里有个快递 是Martin Channing
Hi, I have a delivery for Caroline Channing
送给Caroline Channing的
from Martin Channing.
哦 这是我爸爸给我的礼物
Oh, it's a birthday gift from my daddy
从监狱寄过来的
all the way from prison.
去年 他给了我
Last year, he made me
一个通心粉做的艺术画架
a macaroni art picture frame.
他可是曾经把迈阿密
I mean, the man once rented Miami
租给一个朋友开单身派对的人
for a friend's bachelor party.
嘿 那个画架让我们饱餐了两天
Hey, that picture frame fed us for two days.
这东西不是意大利面
Yeah, well, this thing is not pasta,
它大得进不了门
and it's too big to fit through the door.
三个月前 我也是这样
And so was I three months ago.
是真的
No, really.
我以前坐飞机都得坐第三排
My seat on an airplane used to be Row Three.
就在这街上了
There it is in the street.
一个塞满汉堡肉的避孕套?
A condom full of hamburger meat?
天啊
Oh, my God.
那是兰博基尼吗?
Is that a Lamborghini?
等等
Wait.
那是我的兰博基尼吗?
Is that my Lamborghini?
是的 这是兰博基尼阿文泰德双人敞篷跑车
Yeah, it's a Lamborghini Aventador Roadster.
哇
Wow.
监狱的艺术和工艺已经这么棒了
Prison arts and crafts has gotten pretty fancy.
定制这款车要四年
Well, it takes four years for these cars to be custom-made.
这一辆是在2011年买的
This one was ordered in 2011.
没错 就在我爹还有钱的时候
That's right, my father ordered this for me
买了这个给我
when he still had money.
纠正 是在他还有别人的钱的时候
Correction: When he had everyone else's money.
我爸爸只给过我一个有问题的染色体
All my father ever gave me was that one iffy chromosome.
这给你
Well, here you go.
它是你的了
It's all yours.
我要走回家了
I'm gonna walk home.
这是健康的选择
It's all about healthy choices.
我有车了!
I got a car!
我们有车了!
We got a car!
该死 有人把这蝙蝠车刷成白的了
Damn, someone painted the Batmobile white.
我们还有什么得不到的吗?
Can't we have anything?
这是一辆四十五万美元的跑车
That's a $450,000 sports car.
我知道
I know.
再加个折叠式洗衣烘干机和一辆房车
Add a stackable washer/dryer and a motor home,
就像Caroline赢了"展品争夺战"(游戏)
and it's like Caroline won the Showcase Showdown.
它能在二点九秒内提速到一百
It goes from 0 to 100 in 2.9 seconds.
说到"点"
And speaking of seconds,
我正要在"双靴"点些吃的
I'm getting seconds at Two Boots,
那个富婆就结账了
and that rich bitch is paying.
退后 "东京漂移"
Back off, Tokyo Drift.
这是我们逃跑的车
This is our getaway car.
我这话的意思是离它远点
And by that, I mean get away from it.
要知道 一旦你把这车开出去了
You know, a car like this depreciates 50%
就会贬值一半
the minute you drive it off the lot.
所以我才开我的丰田雅力士
That's why I drive my Toyota Yaris.
哦啦啦
Ooh la la.
吹牛老爹(歌手)在这儿吗?
Is P. Diddy here?
等等 是泰德・特纳(媒体业巨头)吗?
Wait a minute. Is it Ted Turner?
这不是什么名人的
No one cool owns it.
是Caroline的
It's Caroline's.
现在 这种车会让我
Now, this is the kind of car
对任何事情都说同意
that I would say yes to anything in.
除了"更年期音乐"(节目)的票
Anything except tickets to Menopause The Musical.
嘿 Caroline 好车啊
Oh, hey, Caroline. Nice car.
我一直喜欢你多过喜欢Max
I always liked you more than Max.
你知道的吧 妹子
You know that, right, girl?
真的吗?
Really?
因为昨天 我听见你对Max喊
'Cause yesterday, I heard you yell to Max,
"Caroline是快要到47还是48岁了吗"
"Is Caroline turning 47 or 48?
"因为她表现得像个65岁的人"
"Cause she acts like she's 65."
我是说了
Yeah.
因为我想知道在送你的生日卡上要写些什么才好
Yeah, I wanted to know what to write in your birthday card.
大家都离车远点
Well, everyone away from the car.
我刚跟我爸打完电话
I just got off the phone with my dad.
这车明早就要被警察封了
The car is being seized in the morning.
原来是他们不准让我保留自己的生日礼物
Turns out they won't let me keep my present.
就像我八岁时的生日
It's just like my eighth birthday
他们硬要我退回父母送的麦考利・库尔金(童星)
when they made me return Macaulay Culkin.
他们给你买了个男宠?
They bought you a boy?
你确实曾经富有
You were rich.
哎呀 车在眼前 你却不能开
Oh, boy, the car's right here, and you can't even use it.
就像我请了你们这两个不干活的服务员
That's like me having you two for waitresses.
Caroline 能帮个忙吗?
Caroline, can I ask you a favor?
你不能用那辆车去向Sophie求婚
You're not using the car to propose to Sophie.
你都听到她有多喜欢这车了
You heard how much she liked it.
而且这比我原来的计划更有格调
And it's a little bit classier than my original plan:
原本是在洋克市的烛光宴和斗鸡赛
dinner and a cock fight in Yonkers.
我没在刻意偷听
Not that I'm listening,
但我不想被人在同性恋酒吧里求婚
but I'm not gonna get proposed to at a gay bar.
现在可好 去同性恋酒吧也没戏了
Great, now my gay bar idea is out also.
不可以 Oleg
No, Oleg.
我不能把一辆满身划痕的车还回去
I can't return the car with scratches, dents,
或是得了性病的
or chlamydia.
但我们还可以开那车 对吧?
But we can still drive it, right?
我已经涂了一个月的药啦
I mean, I've been on that cream for like a month.
Max 兰博基尼俱乐部规则的第九条是什么
Max, what is the ninth rule of the Lamborghini Club?
不得在车上喝红色饮品
No red drinks in the car.
我的首要原则是
Here's my number one rule:
要是你逼我睡车上
If you're going to make me sleep in it,
我就得在车上喝东西
I am going to drink in it.
那就小心点
Well, just be careful.
我只剩一条消毒湿巾了
I only have one Clorox wipe
它得用到我下次生日为止
that has to last till my next birthday,
况且它都不大湿润了
and it's already lost a lot of its moisture.
我不明白为什么要空坐在这
I don't see why we have to just sit here.
我们不能开这车
We can't drive it.
我爸说了万一出事
My dad said if anything happens to it,
我们要负责的
we'll be responsible.
哪会发生什么事
What could possibly happen
咱可是抽着大麻直通墨西哥
on a weed run to deep Tijuana?
其实我倒希望自己从没有过这车
You know, I wish this car never came,
从未坐上它
and I wish I never sat in it.
这就跟我不去巴尼精品店一个道理
It's the same reason I don't go to Barneys.
买不起的东西还是离远点好
I don't like to be around things I can't afford anymore.
也跟我不去一元店是同一个道理
Same reason I don't go to the 99 Cent Store.
那边有套Nerf网球
There's a Nerf tennis set
球拍在地上 球在垃圾桶里
half on the floor, half in the bin,
都没被我带回家
none of it going home with me.
我本想以积极的心态度过今年的生日
I was trying to be positive about my birthday this year,
要不是我爸东窗事发
but, Max, if things hadn't happened with my father,
今晚就会是我的魔幻般的庆生夜
tonight would have been a magical birthday for me.
还是有点魔术的
Hey, there was some magic.
我就亲自变没了五杯加伏特酒的雪碧
I personally made five vodka Sprites disappear.
厉害吧
Ta-da!
我或许已经驾着车 开去汉普顿斯
I would've got in the car and driven out to the Hamptons,
还能坐上整晚的沙滩
and we'd sit on the beach all night
吃着一个由当地人抓的龙虾
having lobster caught by one of the townies
边喝香槟 边醉醺醺地自拍
and drink champagne while taking duckface selfies
直到天亮
till the sun came up.
补充一下 我就是你想象中的那个当地人
FYI, I'm the townie in this scenario,
憎恶着你们所有人
and I hate all of you.
现在我却过着最糟糕的生日 和我憧憬的完全不同
Instead of doing any of that, I'm having the worst birthday.
也许黛米・摩尔步入花甲之年
I probably feel worse than Demi Moore did
都没我这么难过
when she turned 50.
洗洗睡吧
Yes, just go to sleep.
明天起来就会感觉好多了
You'll feel better tomorrow when you wake up.
要是那个拿着把刀说捅死我们的人
I mean, if that guy with the switchblade
没有来杀我们的话
doesn't come back like he promised he would.
醒醒 Caroline
Caroline.
Caroline 快起来
Caroline, wake up.
我们到沙滩了
We're at the beach.
我载你来到了汉普顿斯
I drove us out to the Hamptons.
生日快乐
Happy birthday!
我们在汉普顿斯?
We're in the Hamptons?
我们竟然在汉普顿斯?
我们怎么来汉普顿斯的?
How are we in the Hamptons?
我睡了多久?
How long have I been sleeping?
三四个小时吧
Three hours, give or take.
你放了两次屁
You farted twice.
我怎么不会醒来?
How did I not wake up?
是吧 确实很糟糕
I know. It was pretty bad.
你放完那个屁后 我还以为我们路过臭蛋乡了
After that last one, I thought we were going through Egg Town.
Max 你又做坏事了
Max, you did it again.
你给我下了安眠药 是吧?
You roofied me, didn't you?
自然是有的
Of course I did.
你在那边哭喊着嚷嚷关于汉普顿斯的美梦
You were crying and babbling about the Hamptons,
我只能把你放倒啊
so I had to put you down.
你答应过我不会再这么做的
You promised you wouldn't again.
上次我整整昏迷了两天
The last time, I was out for two days.
但我真的想把"权力的游戏"看完啊
Yeah, I really just needed to get through Game of Thrones
特别是看乱伦戏时没人吵我
without someone talking during the incest.
你究竟有啥毛病啊?
What is wrong with you?
有纸笔吗?
Have you got a pen and paper?
你明明知道我不想这么做
You knew I didn't want to do this.
你什么事都不想做 所以我替你做了
You never want to do anything, so I did it for you.
你开走了一辆价值45万的车
You took a $450,000 car,
一辆碰都不该碰的车
a car we're not even supposed to be touching,
还开来汉普顿斯兜风
on a joyride to the Hamptons?
是你想来这的
You wanted to be here.
现在来了
You are here.
就尽管享受吧
Just enjoy it.
我没心情享受
I can't enjoy it.
Scotty 到桥上来
Scotty to the bridge.
我是科克船长
This is Captain Kirk.
斯科迪到桥上来
Scotty to the bridge.
你把车开过沙丘 来这沙滩的?
You drove over the dunes and onto the beach?
不是故意的
Not intentionally.
我试过刹车 但这车像在对我说
I tried to stop it, but this car was like,
冲啊 姑娘
"Mm, no, girl."
天啊
Oh, my God.
车上有划痕吗?
Did it get any scratches?
Max 从车里出来 帮我找找有没划痕
Max, get out of the car, and help me look for scratches.
你说过你来汉普顿斯会开心起来的
You said you were more fun in the Hamptons.
才不是这回事
Not true.
苏禄先生 开炮
Mr. Sulu, fire all phasers.
没划痕 兰博基尼没事
No scratches. The Lamborghini is fine.
多亏了你 我也做了一回租车族
But thanks to you, I'm a Rent-A-Wreck.
行了 该把车开回去了
Come on, we have to get this car back.
会的 真是的 放松点
We will. Jeez, relax.
还有时间呢
We still have time.
听着 你说你想来这
Look, you said you wanted to be here.
现在到了 我们别马上走
You're here, and we are not leaving
你得先享受下这沙滩
till you do something beach-y,
比如踏踏浪
like walk in the water
或者找一下被鲨鱼咬断的残骸
or find a half-eaten lady from Jaws.
没 没门 现在就走
No. No way. Let's go.
就试着脱下鞋子嘛
Just take off your shoes or something.
不要
No.
脱下鞋子 感受下沙滩
Just take off your shoes and feel the sand.
Max! 住手 Max
Max! Max, stop.
我已经好久没有修过脚了
I haven't had a proper pedicure
上一次是在贾斯汀・汀布莱克发单曲之时
since Justin Timberlake released a single.
好了 现在可以动动你的脚了
There. Now move your foot around.
不要
No.
不 不 不
No. No! No.
啊
Oh. Oh, yeah.
感觉好爽
That feels nice.
冰凉的细沙在趾间滑过
The cold sand between my toes.
Max 别看我的脚
But, Max, don't look.
中间的指甲简直惨不忍睹
That middle nail's a horror show.
太晚了
Too late.
有那么一会儿 我还觉得它是颗开心果
I thought it was a pistachio for a second.
Max 你有多喜欢海滩
Max, how much do you love the beach?
我不知道 从来没去过
I don't know. I've never been to one.
你从来没去过海滩?
You've never been to a beach?
那又怎么了?
No. What's the point?
我还没有金属探测仪呢
I don't own a metal detector.
好了 时间到
Well, time's up.
可我们才坐下啊
But we just sat down.
我知道 但如果现在走
I know, but if we leave right now,
那我们就还有时间
we'll still have enough time to blow through
掠过麦当劳汽车餐厅
a McDonald's drive-through
就像"回到未来"演的那样
like something from Back to the Future.
我要把咱们的名字写在沙子上
Well, I'm gonna write our names in the sand
很感谢你给我下药
'cause it was a really nice thing
把我绑架到这里
for you to drug me, kidnap me,
然后偷我的车带我到这里
and steal my car to get me out here.
朋友嘛
Hey, we're friends.
好了 掉个头先
All right, I'll just turn this baby around.
哦噢
Uh-oh.
哦噢什么呀?
What's "uh-oh"?
What is "uh-oh"?
卡在沙子里了?
Are we stuck in the sand?
你这个"哦噢"用得非常到位
You have correctly identified the meaning of "uh-oh."
我们连话都不用说
I love that we don't need full sentences
就能心有灵犀了
to communicate anymore.
再试试
Try it again.
不行
Nope.
从运动员家逃出来
I've had less trouble
都没这么难
getting out of athlete's apartments.
那你得下去推车了
Well, you're gonna have to get out and push.
为什么是我?
Why do I have to push?
因为是你给我下药 绑架我
Because you're the one who drugged me, kidnapped me,
还偷了我的车
and stole my car.
说得好
Exactly.
我都帮你搞定了大部分工作了
I've already done the lion's share of the work.
再说这车是咱俩的
And it's our car.
好吧 我去
Fine, I'll do it.
开门 乌乎拉中尉(星际旅行中"进取号的"总通讯官)
Door's up, Lieutenant Uhura.
都被困在这了 能不贫嘴吗
It stopped being funny when we got stuck.
别担心
God, don't worry.
我曾经徒手把一个
I got a 600-pound woman
600磅重的女人从餐厅座位里弄出来
out of a booth at the diner with my bare hands.
我都毫无惧色
I'm fearless.
和那次一样 把她挂到空挡
Toss her in neutral like I did with that lady.
沙子和高跟鞋 这样不行啊
Sand and heels. Not a good combo.
这样不行啊 不行
Not a good combo. Not a good combo.
没事
Oh, all right.
好了
All right.
油门踩到底
I'm gonna floor it.
等我数到三
On the count of three.
一 二...
One, two...
激动了 有点早
I got excited. I went early.
要是每次听见这句我能有一美元
If I had a dime for every time I heard that,
我都能买下这车了
I could buy this car.
没事 再试一次
All right, let's try again.
一 二...
One, two...
这次绝对是故意的
Okay, that was on purpose.
可能吧
A little bit.
真不敢相信
I can't believe it.
真不敢相信我居然不信
I can't believe that I can't believe it,
可我就是不敢相信
but I really can't believe it.
我们遇到这么大的麻烦
We are in very big trouble,
还被困在汉普顿的最烂的沙滩上
and we're not even in the good Hamptons.
我只是想做点好事
I was trying to do something nice.
第一次 也是最后一次
First time, last time.
你知道你是什么吗?
You know what you are?
你是鲁莽他大爷
You are reckless.
这么长时间
You know, all this time,
我一直以为你是个宝马婊
I thought you were a ride-or-die kind of bitch.
我就是个宝马婊怎样
I am a ride-or-die kind of bitch.
宝马婊是啥意思?
What's a ride-or-die kind of bitch?
你不会是在谷歌吧?
Are you Googling "ride-or-die kind of bitch"?
我倒是想 可只有两格信号
I would be, but I only have two bars.
我们有两条出路:
Look, we have two options:
把车开出去 要么等涨潮了被冲出去
Get the car out of the sand, or let the tide take us.
我把浪潮什么的给标记了
Put a pin in that tide thing,
我还挺喜欢那种声音的
'cause I like the sound of it.
再不把车开回去
We barely have enough time to get this car back to the city,
我们要欠上四十五万美元了
or we owe $450,000.
我只有三块 其中两块还是硬币
And I only have $3, and 2 of it's in nickels.
赶紧上车
Now get in the car.
你都开始囤硬币了
You're hoarding nickels,
而我却从1元店空手而归?
and I'm walking out of the 99 Cent Store empty-handed?
什么日子
Now I'm mad.
准备好
Get ready.
你要干嘛?
What are you doing?
把咱们从这弄走
I'm pushing us out of here.
因为我是个宝马婊!
Because I'm a ride-or-die kind of bitch!
也没准
I think.
踩油门!
Now hit it!
怎么做到的? 用屁把咱们冲出去?
What'd you do? Fart us out of the ditch?
拜托 Caroline 给点油
Seriously, Caroline, step on it.
不行 Max
No, Max.
万一出事故呢
We can't risk getting into an accident.
万一车没毁人没亡怎么办?
What if it's not fatal?
慢吞吞地开兰博基尼就相当于
Driving a Lamborghini slow is like going to Red Lobster
去了红龙虾餐厅却没吃切达小饼
and not getting the Cheddar Bay biscuits.
来吧 趁这机会咱们赶紧享受这车吧
Come on, we got to enjoy this car while we can.
- 踩油门啊  - 好吧
- Hit the gas.  - All right.
我会加速到我停止约会的那个年纪
I'll take it up to the top of my age dating window.
四十
40.
我来帮你加到我自己的限期
And I'll take it to the top of mine.
八十!
80!
来吧
Let go. Have some fun.
别 别推我的腿
No, don't push on my leg!
别推我...
Don't push on my...
爽! 爽!
Yes! Yes!
有史以来最棒的生日!
Best birthday ever!
来点末路狂花的节奏?
Should we Thelma and Louise it?
从悬崖上飞过去?
You mean drive over a cliff?
不是 戴着墨镜牵着手啊
No, I mean wear sunglasses and hold hands.
他们还飞悬崖了?
They drive over a cliff?
我还没看过结局呢
I never saw the end.
姑娘们回来了
There they are.
你们按时把车交回去了?
Did you girls get the car back in time this morning?
正好赶上 得感谢Caroline
Yep, just in time, thanks to Caroline.
一路无视限速牌
She was ignoring speed limit signs
还有那些流浪汉
like she does homeless people.
有个警察说我这车开的
A state trooper called my driving
简直是过失杀人
criminally negligent.
我真是自豪
I was so proud.
我差点就发火了
I might've even gotten emotional,
但是还要说服他们别开罚单
but I had to talk our way out of the ticket,
虽然没穿制服 但还是要专业一点
and I like to be professional when my shirt's off.
你们居然没吃罚单?
You didn't get a ticket?
昨天我光是走进健康食品超市都被抓了
Yesterday, I got arrested for just walking into Whole Foods.
我头发里还有沙子
I can't believe I still have sand in my hair.
你要是只有头发里有沙子
If the only place you still have sand is in your hair,
那真是走运
you're lucky.
我下面就差吐出来个珍珠了
I'm about to make a pearl down there.
你们好啊 穷芭比娃娃们
Oh, hey, there, destitute Barbie.
很遗憾你们失去了那辆车
Sorry you lost the dream car.
我还是坐我的专座吧
Anyway, I'll be in my booth.
Sophie 宝贝
Sophie, beautiful baby...
我已经确定了我的求婚地点
I've narrowed down the site of my proposal
必须符合三个条件
to three options:
第一 我们相遇的地方...
A, the place we met...
第二 我们经常爱爱的地方...
B, the place we've had sex most often...
第三 我们最近一次爱爱的地方...
or C, the place we've had sex most recently.
等等 等等
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
这不就是我的专座吗!
All three of those places are this booth!
没错
That's right.
Sophie Kachinsky啊...
Sophie Kachinsky...
他在餐厅求婚?
He's proposing at the diner?
怎么着? 送个洋葱圈当戒指?
What's he gonna do? Put an onion ring on it?
天...
Oh...
我真喜欢
I love that.
我本来打算拒绝
You know, I was planning on saying no
然后让你求我几个小时 但是...
and making you beg for a few hours, but...
我也好爱你
I just love you too much.
和平常的恶心情节不一样啊
Aw, that's so not as gross as normal.
现在一样了
Now it is.